A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Developing Countries Program, Office Files of Anne C. Kubisch FA524
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Developing Countries Program, Office Files of Anne C. Kubisch
1985-1987
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA524
1.2 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Material more than ten years old is open for scholarly research.
Select individual files are restricted, as noted. Permission to access these files must be obtained from the Ford Foundation before scholarly access is permitted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment. Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Ford Foundation
- Chronological Correspondence Files, I
  - 1985 Chronological Correspondence (1 of 4), Feb-Mar 1985 (Box 1)
  - 1985 Chronological Correspondence (2 of 4), Apr-May 1985 (Box 1)
  - 1985 Chronological Correspondence (3 of 4), Jun-Sep 1985 (Box 1)
  - 1985 Chronological Correspondence (4 of 4), Oct-Dec 1985 (Box 1)
  - 1986 Chronological Correspondence (1 of 3), Jan-Mar 1986 (Box 1)
  - 1986 Chronological Correspondence (2 of 3), Apr-Jul 1986 (Box 1)
  - 1986 Chronological Correspondence (3 of 3), Aug-Dec 1986 (Box 1)
  - 1987 Chronological Correspondence (1 of 4), Jan-Apr 1987 (Box 1)
  - 1987 Chronological Correspondence (2 of 4), May-Jul 1987 (Box 1)
  - 1987 Chronological Correspondence (3 of 4), Aug 1987 (Box 1)
  - 1987 Chronological Correspondence, Unsorted (4 of 4), Jan-Oct 1987 (Box 1)